[{
    "theme": "Los lugares y la orientación",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "the city",
            "answers": ["la ciudad"]
        },
        {
            "question": "restaurant",
            "answers": ["el restaurante"]
        },
        {
            "question": "museum",
            "answers": ["el museo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "tourist office",
            "answers": ["la oficina de turismo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "main square",
            "answers": ["la plaza mayor"]
        },
        {
            "question": "library",
            "answers": ["la biblioteca"]
        },
        {
            "question": "school",
            "answers": ["la escuela"]
        },
        {
            "question": "supermarket",
            "answers": ["el supermercado"]
        },
        {
            "question": "station",
            "answers": ["la estación"]
        },
        {
            "question": "hospital",
            "answers": ["el hospital"]
        },
        {
            "question": "pharmacy",
            "answers": ["la farmacia"]
        },
        {
            "question": "near",
            "answers": ["cerca"]
        },
        {
            "question": "far",
            "answers": ["lejos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "on the right",
            "answers": ["a la derecha"]
        },
        {
            "question": "on the left",
            "answers": ["a la izquierda"]
        },
        {
            "question": "straight ahead",
            "answers": ["todo recto", "todo derecho"]
        },
        {
            "question": "turn right",
            "answers": ["gira a la derecha", "dobla a la derecha"]
        },
        {
            "question": "turn left",
            "answers": ["gira a la izquierda", "dobla a la izquierda"]
        },
        {
            "question": "opposite (in front of)",
            "answers": ["en frente de"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Is the library far from here?",
            "answers": ["¿La biblioteca está lejos de aquí?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Is the museum close to here?",
            "answers": ["¿El museo está cerca de aquí?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "I’m looking for the station",
            "answers": ["Busco la estación"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do I get to the supermarket?",
            "answers": ["¿Cómo llego al supermercado?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the pharmacy?",
            "answers": ["¿Dónde está la farmacia?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Follow the street",
            "answers": ["Sigue la calle"]
        }
    ]
}]